

CONTACT

- +91 9074212751
- muhammeduvais907@gmail.com
- kootilangadi, Malappuram 676506, Kerala, India

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021

Diploma Computer
Engineering

2017 - 2018

 PLUS TWO (Computee Science)

2005 - 2016

 SSLC (Secondary Education)-Kerala state board

PHYSICAL STATUS

• Hearing Impaired Disability: 71%

SKILLS

- Front-end Development
- Back-end Development
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Bootstrap
- Django
- Python
- Git/Github

LANGUAGES

- English
- Malayalam

MUHAMMED UVAIS OK

PYTHON FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

As a Python full-stack developer, I have extensive experience developing and deploying full-stack web applications using Python frameworks such as Django. 1 have strong skills in front-end development and back-end development technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

 GEDEXO DESIGN AND TECHNOLOGY LLP python full-stsck web developer

2023 - PRESENT

- Developed and designed cone sites for clients
- Collaborated with clients and team members to ensure project goals were met
- Provided website maintenance and support to clients

OXDUTECH

python full-stsck web developer

2023 - 2024

- · website developer and website design
- Developed and designed e-commerce websites
- Educational institutions

OBJECTIVE

 To take the challenging and responsive assignment in a reputed and well organised company where I can prove my excellence abilities, skill and my work will be recognized and justified

PORTFOLIO

- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/odadoz-e-commerce.git
- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/danbury.git
- https://github.com/Uvais-ai/mobile-shopil.git